RG 002:004, General Assembly Papers
Connecticut State Library
- 1913-1971, 1984-045
  - 1975
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House (Box 766)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House (Box 767)
    - Unfinished Business - Bank and Regulations; Education, Senate (Box 768)
    - Unfinished Business - Education, House (Box 769)
    - Unfinished Business - Education; Elections, Senate (Box 770)
    - Unfinished Business - Elections, House (Box 771)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment, Senate, House (Box 772)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment; Finance, Senate (Box 773)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance (Box 774)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, House (Box 775)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law (Box 776)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law, House (Box 777)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law, House (Box 778)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law, House, Government Administration and Policy, Senate, House (Box 779)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Policy, House (Box 780)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Rights and Opportunities; Humane Institutions; Human Services (Box 781)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance (Box 782)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate (Box 783)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate (Box 784)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House (Box 785)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House (Box 786)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House; Labor and Industrial Relations (Box 787)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Industrial Relations; Legislative Management (Box 788)
    - Unfinished Business - Liquor Control; Public Health and Safety, Senate (Box 789)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health and Safety, House (Box 790)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Personnel and Military Affairs (Box 791)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Personnel and Military Affairs, Legislative Action, Senate (Box 792)
    - Unfinished Business - Regulations Action, House; Committee Resolutions (Box 793)
    - Unfinished Business - State and Urban Development (Box 794)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation (Box 795)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation (Box 796)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation; Special Session, December (Box 797)
  - 1976
    - (Box 798)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, Senate and Senate Joint (Box 798)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, House 1-69 (Box 798)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, House 70-252 (Box 799)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, House Joint 1-231 (Box 799)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, House Joint, 87-148 (Box 800)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Special Session Resolutions (Box 800)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments (Box 800)
    - Constitutional Amendments (Box 801)
    - Public Acts, 1-69 (Box 801)
    - Public Acts, 70-115 (Box 800)
    - Public Acts, 116-165 (Box 803)
    - Public Acts, 166-218 (Box 804)
    - Public Acts, 219-263 (Box 805)
    - Public Acts, 264-306 (Box 806)
    - Public Acts, 307-344 (Box 807)
    - Public Acts, 345-383 (Box 808)
    - Public Acts, 384-413 (Box 809)
    - Public Acts, 414-435 (Box 810)
    - Public Acts, 436 (Box 811)
    - Public Acts, 436 (Box 812)
    - Special Acts, 1-54 (Box 813)
    - Special Acts, 55-88 (Box 814)
    - Rejected Bills (Box 814)
    - Resolutions Withdrawn (Box 814)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate (Box 815)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House (Box 816)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House; Banks, Senate and House (Box 817)
    - Unfinished Business - Education, Senate and House (Box 818)
    - Unfinished Business - Education, House; Elections; Environment (Box 819)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Senate and House (Box 820)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, House; General Law (Box 821)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Policy; Humane Institutions; Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 822)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate and House (Box 823)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House (Box 824)
    - Unfinished Business - Legislative; Liquor Control; Public Personnel and Military Affairs; Regulation Actions; Energy (Box 825)
    - Unfinished Business - Resolutions (Box 826)
    - Unfinished Business - State and Urban Development (Box 826)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation (Box 826)
  - 1977
    - (Box 827)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, Senate and Senate Joint (Box 827)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, House 1-203 (Box 828)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, House 204-305, House Joint, 210-262 (Box 829)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Trailer Session, July 25 - Resolutions (Box 829)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments (Box 829)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, Senate and Senate Joint, 20-55 (Box 829)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - House Resolutions, 306-412 (Box 830)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Trailer Session, July 25 - Resolutions, House Joint (Box 830)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments, Senate Joint 57-126 (Box 831)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments, House and House Joint (Box 831)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Initiation of Local Legislation (Box 831)
    - Public Acts, 1-34 (Box 831)
    - Public Acts, 35-104 (Box 832)
    - Public Acts, 105-158 (Box 833)
    - Public Acts, 159-209 (Box 834)
    - Public Acts, 210-260 (Box 835)
    - Public Acts, 261-298 (Box 836)
    - Public Acts, 299-340 (Box 837)
    - Public Acts, 341-370 (Box 838)
    - Public Acts, 371-414 (Box 839)
    - Public Acts, 415-447 (Box 840)
    - Public Acts, 448-473 (Box 841)
    - Public Acts, 474-503 (Box 842)
    - Public Acts, 504-535 (Box 843)
    - Public Acts, 536-488 (Box 844)
    - Public Acts 489-544 (Box 845)
    - Public Acts, 566-587 (Box 846)
    - Public Acts 588-602 (Box 847)
    - Public Acts, 603-607 (Box 848)
    - Public Acts, 608-614 (Box 849)
    - Special Acts, 1-46 (Box 850)
    - Special Acts, 47-90 (Box 851)
    - Special Acts, 91-98 (Box 852)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate (Box 853)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate and House (Box 854)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House (Box 855)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House (Box 856)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House; Banks; Education; Senate (Box 857)
    - Unfinished Business - Education, Senate (Box 858)
    - Unfinished Business - Elections (Box 859)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment (Box 860)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Senate (Box 861)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Senate and House (Box 862)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, House (Box 863)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, House (Box 864)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law, Senate and House (Box 865)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law, House (Box 866)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law, House; Government Administration and Policy, Senate (Box 867)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law, House; Government Administration and Policy, Senate and House (Box 868)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Policy, House (Box 869)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Rights and Opportunities; Human Services (Box 870)
    - Unfinished Business - Humane Institutions, Senate and House; Insurance and Real Estate, Senate and House (Box 871)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate; House; Judiciary, Senate (Box 872)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate (Box 873)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate and House (Box 874)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House (Box 875)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House (Box 876)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Industrial Relations (Box 877)
    - Unfinished Business - Legislative Management; Liquor Control; Public Health and Safety (Box 878)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health and Safety; Public Personnel and Military Affairs (Box 879)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Personnel and Military Affairs; Regulatory Actions (Box 880)
    - Unfinished Business - Regulatory Action; State and Urban Development, Senate (Box 881)
    - Unfinished Business - State and Urban Development, Senate; Transportation, Senate (Box 882)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation, Senate and House (Box 883)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation, House (Box 884)
  - 1978
    - (Box 885)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, Senate (Box 885)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Trailer Session, June 19 - Resolutions (Box 885)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, Senate Joint to 170 (Box 885)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, Senate Joint, House to 219 (Box 886)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, House 221-455 (Box 887)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, House, 456-527 (Box 888)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments (Box 889)
    - Public Acts, 1-64 (Box 890)
    - Public Acts, 65-111 (Box 891)
    - Public Acts, 112-140 (Box 892)
    - Public Acts, 141-175 (Box 893)
    - Public Acts, 176-208 (Box 894)
    - Public Acts, 209-226 (Box 895)
    - Public Acts, 227-255 (Box 896)
    - Public Acts, 256-280 (Box 897)
    - Public Acts, 281-303 (Box 898)
    - Public Acts, 304-325 (Box 899)
    - Public Acts, 326-345 (Box 900)
    - Public Acts, 346-375 (Box 901)
    - Public Acts, 376-380 (Box 902)
    - Special Acts, 1-36 (Box 903)
    - Special Acts, 37-81 (Box 903)
    - Rejected Bills (Box 904)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate (Box 904)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate and House (Box 905)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House (Box 906)
    - Unfinished Business - Banks; Education; Elections; Environment (Box 907)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Senate and House (Box 908)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, House; General Law, Senate and House (Box 909)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Policy (Box 910)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Policy; Human Rights and Opportunities; Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate (Box 911)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 912)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House (Box 913)
    - Unfinished Business - Liquor Control; Public Health and Safety; Public Personnel and Military Affairs (Box 914)
    - Unfinished Business - Regulatory Actions; Urban Development; Transportation (Box 915)
  - 1979
    - (Box 916)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions (Box 916)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, Senate Joint; Special Session, July and October; House 1-105 (Box 917)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, House 107-313 (Box 918)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, House 314-533 (Box 919)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, House 534-581; Special Session, July and October; Joint Resolutions, 1-72 (Box 920)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Joint Resolutions, 173-307; Special Session, July and October (Box 921)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments; Junior Appointments; Special Session Appointments; Withdrawn Resolutions; Constitutional Amendments (Box 922)
    - Special Session, July and December (Box 923)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreement (Box 923)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreement (Box 924)
    - Public Acts, 1-60 (Box 925)
    - Public Acts, 61-120 (Box 926)
    - Public Acts, 121-153 (Box 927)
    - Public Acts, 154-210 (Box 928)
    - Public Acts, 211-246 (Box 929)
    - Public Acts, 247-298 (Box 930)
    - Public Acts, 299-347 (Box 931)
    - Public Acts, 348-376 (Box 932)
    - Public Acts, 377-404 (Box 933)
    - Public Acts, 405-435 (Box 934)
    - Public Acts, 436-470 (Box 935)
    - Public Acts, 471-504 (Box 936)
    - Public Acts, 505-534 (Box 937)
    - Public Acts, 535-559 (Box 938)
    - Public Acts, 560-577 (Box 939)
    - Public Acts, 578-600 (Box 940)
    - Public Acts, 601-610 (Box 941)
    - Public Acts, 610-625 (Box 942)
    - Public Acts, 626-631 (Box 943)
    - Special Session (Box 944)
    - Special Acts, 1-33 (Box 944)
    - Special Acts, 34-87 (Box 945)
    - Special Session, Special Acts (Box 946)
    - Rejected Bills (Box 947)
    - Rejected Bills (Box 948)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate Joint and Senate (Box 949)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate, House Joint and House (Box 950)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House (Box 951)
    - Unfinished Business - Banks, Senate and House; Education, Senate (Box 952)
    - Unfinished Business - Education, House; Energy and Public Utilities, Senate (Box 953)
    - Unfinished Business - Energy and Public Utilities, Senate; Special Session, October (Box 954)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment, House and Senate (Box 955)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment, Senate; Executive and Legislative Nominations, Senate; Finance, Revenue and Bond, Senate (Box 956)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bond, Senate and House (Box 957)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bond, House (Box 958)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bond, House (Box 959)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bond, Special Session (Box 960)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law, Senate and House Special Session (Box 961)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections, Senate (Box 962)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections, Senate and House (Box 963)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections, House; Human Services (Box 964)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Services, House; Insurance and Real Estate, Senate (Box 965)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate, House; Judiciary, Senate (Box 966)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate (Box 967)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate (Box 968)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House (Box 969)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House (Box 970)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House (Box 971)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Public Employees, House; Planning and Development, Senate (Box 972)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development, Senate, House, Special Session (Box 973)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health (Box 974)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Safety; Transportation, Senate and House (Box 975)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation, House, Special Session; No Committee Name (Box 976)
  - 1980
    - (Box 977)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions (Box 977)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Trailer Session, June 16 - Resolutions (Box 977)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Constitutional Amendments (Box 977)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments (Box 978)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreements (Box 979)
    - Public Acts, 1-69 (Box 980)
    - Public Acts, 70-79 (Box 981)
    - Public Acts, 80-156 (Box 982)
    - Public Acts, 157-204 (Box 983)
    - Public Acts, 205-254 (Box 984)
    - Public Acts, 255-284 (Box 985)
    - Public Acts, 285-314 (Box 986)
    - Public Acts, 315-357 (Box 987)
    - Public Acts, 358-394 (Box 988)
    - Public Acts, 395-421 (Box 989)
    - Public Acts, 422-442 (Box 990)
    - Public Acts, 443-467 (Box 991)
    - Public Acts, 468-475 (Box 992)
    - Public Acts, 476-481 (Box 993)
    - Public Acts, 482 (Box 994)
    - Public Acts, 483 (Box 995)
    - Public Acts, 484 (Box 996)
    - Special Acts, 1-41 (Box 997)
    - Special Acts, 42-80 (Box 998)
    - Rejected Bills (Box 999)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 1000)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 1001)
    - Unfinished Business - Banks; Education; Energy and Public Utilities (Box 1002)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment, Senate, House; Finance, Revenue and Bond, Senate (Box 1003)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bond, Senate, House (Box 1004)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bond, House; General Law, Senate (Box 1005)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law, House; Government Administration and Elections (Box 1006)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections, House; Human Services, Senate, House (Box 1007)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary (Box 1008)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House (Box 1009)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House; Legislative Management; Labor and Public Employees; Planning and Development, Senate (Box 1010)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development, Senate, House; Public Health (Box 1011)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Safety (Box 1012)
  - 1981
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions (Box 1013)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Trailer Session, July 20 Resolutions (Box 1013)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Special Session, November 19 Resolutions (Box 1013)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Special Session, February 22, 1982 Resolutions (Box 1013)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Constitutional Amendments (Box 1013)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments (Box 1013)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreement (Box 1014)
    - Plan of Reapportionment (Box 1014A)
    - Public Acts, 1-36 (Box 1015)
    - Public Acts, 37-79 (Box 1016)
    - Public Acts, 80-115 (Box 1017)
    - Public Acts, 116-145 (Box 1018)
    - Public Acts, 146-170 (Box 1019)
    - Public Acts, 171-200 (Box 1020)
    - Public Acts, 201-225 (Box 1021)
    - Public Acts, 226-254 (Box 1022)
    - Public Acts, 255-275 (Box 1023)
    - Public Acts, 276-300 (Box 1024)
    - Public Acts, 301-330 (Box 1025)
    - Public Acts, 331-350 (Box 1026)
    - Public Acts, 351-365 (Box 1027)
    - Public Acts, 366-383 (Box 1028)
    - Public Acts, 384-399 (Box 1029)
    - Public Acts, 400-420 (Box 1030)
    - Public Acts, 421-435 (Box 1031)
    - Public Acts, 436-446 (Box 1032)
    - Public Acts, 447-460 (Box 1033)
    - Public Acts, 461-471 (Box 1034)
    - Public Acts, 472-473 (Box 1035)
    - Special Acts, 1-11 (Box 1035)
    - Special Session, November - Public Acts, 1-14 (Box 1036)
    - Special Acts, 12-34 (Box 1037)
    - Special Acts, 35-67 (Box 1038)
    - Special Acts, 68-74, Special Acts Special Session, Rejected Bills (Box 1039)
    - Rejected Bills (Box 1040)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate (Box 1041)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate, House (Box 1042)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House (Box 1043)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House; Education, Senate (Box 1044)
    - Unfinished Business - Education, House (Box 1045)
    - Unfinished Business - Energy and Public Utilities, Senate, House (Box 1046)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment, Senate, House (Box 1047)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bond, Senate (Box 1048)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bond, Senate, House (Box 1049)
    - Unfinished Business - Revenue and Bond, House (Box 1050)
    - Unfinished Business - Revenue and Bond, House; General Law, Senate (Box 1051)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law, House; Government Administration and Elections, Senate (Box 1052)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections, Senate, House (Box 1053)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Elections, House (Box 1054)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Services; Insurance and Real Estate (Box 1055)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate, House; Judiciary, Senate (Box 1056)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate (Box 1057)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate, House (Box 1058)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House (Box 1059)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House (Box 1060)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Public Employees (Box 1061)
    - Unfinished Business - Legislation Management; Planning and Development (Box 1062)
    - Unfinished Business - Planning and Development, House; Public Health, Senate, House (Box 1063)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health, House; Public Safety; Transportation, Senate (Box 1064)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation, Senate, House (Box 1065)
    - Unfinished Business - Special Session, November (Box 1066)
  - 1982
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions (Box 1067)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Special Session, June 28 (Box 1067)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Constitutional Amendments (Box 1067)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments (Box 1068)
    - Special Session, June - Collective Bargaining Agreements (Box 1069)
    - Special Session, June - Collective Bargaining Agreements (Box 1070)
    - Public Acts, 1-49 (Box 1071)
    - Public Acts, 50-95 (Box 1072)
    - Public Acts, 96-145 (Box 1073)
    - Public Acts, 146-160 (Box 1074)
    - Public Acts, 161-195 (Box 1075)
    - Public Acts, 196-217 (Box 1076)
    - Public Acts, 219-229 (Box 1077)
    - Public Acts, 230-247 (Box 1078)
    - Public Acts, 248-259 (Box 1079)
    - Public Acts, 260-299 (Box 1080)
    - Public Acts, 300-320 (Box 1081)
    - Public Acts, 321-345 (Box 1082)
    - Public Acts, 346-365 (Box 1083)
    - Public Acts, 366-389 (Box 1084)
    - Public Acts, 390-414 (Box 1085)
    - Public Acts, 415-426 (Box 1086)
    - Public Acts, 427-441 (Box 1087)
    - Public Acts, 442-465 (Box 1088)
    - Public Acts, 466-472, Special Session, June 28 (Box 1089)
    - Special Acts, 1-21 (Box 1090)
    - Special Acts, 22-56 (Box 1091)
    - Rejected Bills (Box 1092)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 1093)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House (Box 1094)
    - Unfinished Business - Banks; Education (Box 1095)
    - Unfinished Business - Energy and Public Utilities; Environment; Finance, Revenue and Bond (Box 1096)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bond (Box 1097)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bond, House (Box 1098)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Revenue and Bond, House (Box 1099)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Election, House; Human Services (Box 1100)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary, Senate (Box 1101)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate, House (Box 1102)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Public Employees; Legislative Management; Planning and Development (Box 1103)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health; Public Safety; Transportation (Box 1104)
  - 1983
    - Constitutional Amendments - Resolutions from January, July, October, and December (Box 1105)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments (Box 1106)
    - Regular Session and Special Session, July - Collective Bargaining Agreements (Box 1107)
    - Public Acts, 1-49 (Box 1108)
    - Public Acts, 50-100 (Box 1109)
    - Public Acts, 51-150 (Box 1110)
    - Public Acts, 151-195 (Box 1111)
    - Public Acts, 196-230 (Box 1112)
    - Public Acts, 231-275 (Box 1113)
    - Public Acts, 276-320 (Box 1114)
    - Public Acts, 321-326 (Box 1115)
    - Public Acts, 361-390 (Box 1116)
    - Public Acts, 391-411 (Box 1117)
    - Public Acts, 412-450 (Box 1118)
    - Public Acts, 451-474 (Box 1119)
    - Public Acts, 475-490 (Box 1120)
    - Public Acts, 491-520 (Box 1121)
    - Public Acts, 521-540 (Box 1122)
    - Public Acts, 541-564 (Box 1123)
    - Public Acts, 565-579 (Box 1124)
    - Public Acts, 580-587 (Box 1125)
    - Special Session - Public Acts, 1-14 (Box 1126)
    - Public Acts - Public Acts, 15-39 (Box 1127)
    - Special Acts, 1-55 (Box 1128)
    - Special Session - Special Acts (Box 1129)
    - Special Session - Special Acts (Box 1130)
    - Rejected Bills (Box 1131)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate (Box 1132)